Hey, howdy there, Mr. Lee.
What is this? Filipino New Year's?
No. Why you say that?
Because you're cooking up a feast.
I can smell it all the way
from the interstate.
What is that? Barbecue?
Oh, yeah. But it not coming from here.
What is that noise?
Daddy!
- Daddy!
What is your take on this, Jerry?
The people are gonna love it,
Mr. President.
Our only conflict is whether we ambush
the 6:00 news or hold out for prime time.
Screw the press.
This is a need-to-know situation.
We should make it top secretÉ
É and move in right away
with DEFCON 4.
Mr. President, we cannot sit on this.
General Casey, do you have an opinion?
Well, sir, do we know they're hostile?
What do you mean,
"do we know they're hostile?"
They have our planet surrounded
with thousands of warships.
Do we know they're warships?
Professor, what do we know about them?
We know they're extremely advanced
technologicallyÉ
É which suggests, very rightfully so,
that they're peaceful.
An advanced civilization is,
by definition, not barbaric.
Mr. President, this is a great day.
I and all my colleagues
are extremely excited.
Good.
Extraterrestrial life.
You're right, Jerry.
The people are gonna love it.
This is a momentous occasion.
- Mr. President, we have to actÑ
- We'll go all media on this.
I'll wear my blue Cerruti suit.
And, Jerry, I'll need a good speech.
Statesman-likeÉ
É historical and yet warm and neighborly.
Abraham Lincoln meets Leave It to Beaver.
You know the sort of thing. Heh.
Yes, sir.
- Are they too old-fashioned?
- Yes.
No, I don't think so.
This has got the colors, but no.
I don't think so.
- Not vivid enough.
- Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
- Nancy had this in the library, didn't she?
- Yes, indeed.
I don't think so.
I thought perhaps the watered silk.
And this week it's on sale.
I hardly think I need worry about that.
My husband is the leader
of the free world.
What do you think, Taffy?
Why don't you leave the Roosevelt Room
the way the Roosevelts wanted it?
Because Eleanor Roosevelt
was too fond of chintz. That's why.
Mother, this isn't your house.
Taffy, if you're going to be a pest,
I'm going to ignore you.
- Mrs. Dale?
- Yes?
- I saw you fight Sonny Liston in '69.
- Really?
- You mean, you were a nun back then?
- Oh, yes.
We've always been fight fans,
haven't we, sisters?
Byron Williams, telephone.
- Byron WilliamsÉ
- That's me. I gotta go.
You ladies have a nice time, all right?
Thank you.
- Yeah?
- Byron?
Oh, Louise.
I'm sorry I have to call you at work.
The boys haven't been home in two nights
and I don't know what to do.
Listen, you're doing the best you can.
They're just at that age.
Louise, the casino manager's
giving me the evil eye. I've gotta go.
I'll call you later, okay?
Hey, are you still cool on me
coming to Washington?
Sure. Of course I am.
You take care, okay? Bye.
AhhÉ
Do you have to drink in front of me?
You're an adult. Just cope.
It doesn't help me
that all we ever do is sit around in bars.
Hey. This is work, baby, okay?
I'm checking the decor,
the lighting, the traffic flow.
If I'd known you'd turn into a crook,
I never would have married you.
I'm not a crook.
I'm ambitious. There's a difference.
And if you think you can make
a nickel in this townÉ
É without knowing how to dally
around a few curves, wellÉ
É you don't know doodlysquat
about the gaming industry.
Oh, Art.
Galaxy's gonna be
the best hotel in Vegas.
The best. I promise.
Don't you realize what you're doing?
Destroying the Earth.
All this greed. This money system.
You're destroying everything.
Okay, okay, Barbara. Okay.
Keep your voice down.
I got friends here.
Sugar. Hit me one more time.
- Stop flirting with the waitress.
- Oh, God. Here.
Go on over to the rouletteÉ
É play our anniversaryÉ
É and stay off of black.
Thanks, honey.
Yeah?
Make it quick.
We go out live in 10 minutes.
What? The actual president?
What do you mean, "cutting in"?
Budget negotiations may be dead
in the water after this week.
Hair looks good.
I like the hair.
Ñquote, "factually challenged."
Griffin saysÉ
Yeah, Stone. Speak.
Jason, hi, it's me.
You wearing a bra?
Listen, this is big. President Dale
is cutting into my show today.
That's absurd. Why would he stoop
to being on Today in Fashion?
He's interrupting everybody.
I don't know, it's some sort of
emergency announcement or something.
This doesn't make sense.
He should be talking to us.
White House is coming out live.
Good evening, my fellow Americans.
I apologize for interrupting
your regular programsÉ
É but I have a very important
announcement to make.
Many important things have happened
to me in my life:
My graduation from PrincetonÉ
É the day that Marsha said
she would be my wifeÉ
É the birth of our daughter, Taffy.
Thanks, Dad.
And the news that I have heard todayÉ
- É ranks right up there.
- Thank you.
A powerful memory is in the making.
Not just for meÉ
É but for all mankind.
Today, an extraordinary discovery
was made by the Hubble telescope.
The data from the Hubble was decodedÉ
É then analyzed
by the most powerful computers at MIT.
The images are undeniable.
We are entering the dawn of a new era.
Frame enlargements
provide an astonishing sight.
A fleet of vehicles,
which can best be described asÉ
É flying saucers.
Come on. Come on.
Papa needs a new pair of shoes.
Hey!
Hey, am I the only one
shooting craps here?
Ñwe will have
the opportunity to meet with them.
I feel this is the perfect summation
to the 20th centuryÉ
Martians.
This is great.
Please come to Earth. Please.
We need you.
I got people coming in.
Everybody wants to be a part of this.
Galaxy's gonna be world-class.
And soonÉ
É we will become one solar system.
What the hell is he talking about?
These flying saucers
have come from the planet MarsÉ
- É and at their current course and speedÉ
- Oh. Hey.
Listen, Hoss. I've been thinking about
Martians when there wasn't no Martians.
It is profoundly moving
to know there is intelligent life out there.
Glad they got it somewhere.
And our world will never feel
quite the same again.
Good nightÉ
É and God bless you all.
ThisÉ
É is intense.
Shut up, Poppy. Shut up.
Shut up.
Jason Stone.
It's for you.
Poppy, honey. No, sweetie.
That's right. Shh. Good girl. Yeah?
Yeah. Well, I could be there atÉ
É I don't know, 11.
Okay, bye-bye.
Yes?
Oh, they want me to go interview
that professor from the White House.
Kessler?
- Donald Kessler?
- Yeah, I think that was his name.
You know, the science guy.
This is nuts, this isÉ
We should have got that guy.
Well, I can't help it
if your people are too slow.
Right, Poppy?
- Finished!
- One minute, 57 seconds.
- Ha-ha! Didn't I tell you under two minutes?
- You did.
You did. I'm so proud of you.
- Hey, Ma, you want a doughnut?
- How old are they?
Fresh-baked Monday.
Richie, that's six days ago.
Okay, give me a couple.
Hey, this Martian thing
is pretty awesome, huh?
Did any one of you traitors
see my Muffy?
Your brother's gonna volunteer.
As soon as I get back to the base.
- Volunteer for what, Billy Glenn?
- Martian detail.
- Uh-huh.
- Cool.
If any of them Martians
come around hereÉ
É I'm gonna kick their butts.
Heh-heh-heh.
Jump!
Excuse me, folks,
but we gotta make an unscheduled stop.
It's Mama.
What are you doing here? Huh?
If you ain't home, why ain't you in class?
- Mama, class was canceled.
- Class was not canceled.
- Come here. Come here.
- For what?
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Now, come here.
Let go of him.
Okay. Now, just come here.
Come here.
Think it's smart to cut school?
- What are you doing?
- Do you? Do you? Huh? Huh?
- No.
- "No, Mama." It's dumb.
- You're gonna flunk and go to jail.
- No.
Get your butt on the bus.
Get on that bus, boy.
I'll be tripping all over you.
Get back there.
- I don't want to hear another word.
- I hate school.
I heard that.
- Hi.
- Hi there.
- Want a date?
- How about it?
A date?
Sounds good.
The stress at work isÉ
É unbelievable.
Mr. Bava, can I speak to you in private?
No, I gotta watch the floor.
What do you want, Byron?
- I'm supporting my family back East.
- I thought you were divorced.
Well, I am,
but I still have to take care of them.
Anyway, look. Things have been
a little lean around hereÉ
É and I was wondering
if I could get a raise?
- Out of the question.
- Mr. Bava, I'm an asset to this hotel.
- I mean, they like me around here.
- Byron, you're a nice guy.
But I can get Leon Spinks or Buster Douglas
for the same money, maybe less.
You better get moving.
You're on in five minutes.
This show's gonna get
a hell of a rating.
It's all yours, Ian.
Ñlanguage you choose to employ,
and in certain circumstancesÉ
É the proposition that two and two
equals fiveÉ
É is entirely legitimate.
Call me Nathalie.
And you, do please call me Donald.
I've always admired your show.
Really? You like my work?
Yes. Very much.
WhyÉ
Why, thank you.
Coming out of commercial.
In five, four, three, twoÉ
Welcome back. We're speaking
with Professor Donald Kessler.
He's the chairman
of the American Academy of Astronautics.
ProfessorÉ
É isn't it weird that we sent
a space probe to MarsÉ
É and we didn't even find anyone?
Well, not really, NathalieÉ
É because we didn't get into the canals.
The Martian canals are actually canyons.
Some of them are over 100 miles deep.
The Martian civilization
has clearly developedÉ
É under the surface of the planet.
Their science and technology
must be absolutely mind-boggling.
So, what, in your view, Donald KesslerÉ
É chairman, are some of the things
that the Martians can teach us, professor?
Quite a lot about Mars, I expect, Nathalie.
She's flirting with him.
Ahem. But seriously,
this is tremendously exciting.
Think of it. The knowledge, new ideas.
It's gonna change everything.
And we must be open to it.
Maybe they can tell us
about our universe.
How it started. Where it's going.
Perhaps even its purpose.
It's tremendously exciting.
This is the most important thing to happen
since Jesus walked in Galilee.
Oh, Christ. What's wrong with the picture?
Go to Camera 2!
I can't. It's busted.
Well, then go to 1. Go to 4.
He just copped a feel.
Now what?
What's that?
So that's a Martian.
That's a Martian?
- Oh, my God.
- Yikes.
I'm not gonna have that thing
in my house.
Sweetie, we may have to. The people
will expect me to meet with them.
Well, they're not gonna eat off
the Van Buren china.
Oh, look at that brain.
He must be real smart.
It's gross.
Don't forget, NathalieÉ
É that we will look equally gross to him.
Whoa. He made the international sign
of the doughnut.
From the limited information available,
I've made three extrapolations.
One, our Martian friend
is a carbon-based life form.
Two, he breathes nitrogen.
And three,
the large cerebrum here indicatesÉ
É telepathic potential.
You mean they can read our thoughts?
- Potentially, yes.
- What about their intentions?
Are they a friendly people?
Logic dictates that given their extremely
high level of technical developmentÉ
É they're an advanced cultureÉ
É therefore, peaceful and enlightened.
The human race, on the other handÉ
É is an aggressively dangerous species.
Now, I suspect they have
more to fear from usÉ
É than we from them.
- Doctor.
- Thank you, professor.
For many years,
I've been refining a translating computer.
The results are not perfectÉ
É but this may answer
some of your questions.
All green of skinÉ
É 800 centuries ago.
Their bodily fluids
include the birth of half-breeds.
- How many centuries did he say?
- Eight hundred, sir.
Ñself-determination of the cosmos.
For dark is the suede
that mows like a harvest.
What the hell does that mean?
- Hey, Mitch.
- Good morning, miss.
I'm sorry, you can't come this way.
There's a tour in progress.
Oh.
Hello, my name is Barbara.
Hello, Barbara.
I am an alcoholic,
but I haven't had a drink in three months.
Thank you.
I'm feeling so optimistic
because of the Martians.
We're not alone in the universe.
And it's so perfectÉ
É that it's happening at the beginning
of the new millennium.
Our planet was suffering
with the ozone and the rain forestÉ
É and so many people
unhappy in their lives.
And then the Martians heard
our global karmic cry for help.
People say they're uglyÉ
É but I think they've come
to show us the way.
I think they've come to save us.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
You be careful, baby, okay?
Don't get yourself killed.
Oh, ain't she cute?
- Son, we're real proud of you.
- Thanks, Dad.
Let me take this.
- So long, bro.
- So long, retard.
Just don't be touching none of my stuff
while I'm gone.
Bye-bye, Grandma.
Goodbye, Thomas.
It's Billy Glenn, Grandma.
I know. Thomas. Ha-ha-ha.
Bye-bye, honey.
I got to go.
All right.
I love you, baby.
Adios.
Be careful, boy.
Bye-bye.
Well, he'll be all right.
- I hope so.
- Army trains them good.
Well, he's gone for a while.
Oh, Richie, why can't you be more
like your brother?
Darling, we got plumb lucky
with Billy Glenn.
Can't expect the same luck twice.
Richie, want to make yourself
useful for a change?
- Sure, Dad.
- Take Grandma back to the home.
Grandma, I bet you never thought you'd
live to see the Martians coming to Earth.
It's pretty far out, huh?
Just think of all the crazy stuff
you must have seen in your lifetime.
I bet people were pretty scared
when they invented the train.
Come on, kid, I'm not that old.
Grandma, are you okay?
I want to see Slim.
I want to see SlimÉ
É and Muffy and Richie.
Grandma, I'm Richie.
I know, Thomas.
Richie was always the best one.
The president is talking
to other world leaders.
They're preparing a list of issues
of common interest to discuss.
There is a unilateral, concerted,
diplomatic effort being made.
- Jason.
- Yeah, Jerry, thanks.
If the Martians land,
will the press have access?
Can we do interviews?
Well, I mean, that depends.
You know,
we'd have to establish contactÉ
É work out whatever
communication problemsÉ
É establish a parameter for talks. Then
I guess we just see what happens. Heh-heh.
Oh, here's the president.
Good morning.
It's nice to see you all again.
I just have a few minutes for questions,
so let's get started.
Mr. President!
Do the Martians have two sexes,
like we do?
From Hollywood, we bring
you The Lawrence Welk Show.
Now, here he is, Mr. Music-Maker himself,
Lawrence Welk.
This pussycat
is the most beautiful pussycatÉ
É in the whole world.
That's my Muffy.
Mwah.
Richie, didn't you ever have
a pussycat of your own?
Sure, Grandma.
Music.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Hey, Grandma, you gonna be okay?
If you need anything,
any doughnuts or anythingÉ
É give me a call, all right?
Bye.
Will you answer too
How do, Byron?
Looks like you ain't got no wheels.
Come on, get in.
I'm gonna do you a favor, Byron.
I owe you one. I made a ton of money
on your last fight in '73.
The Quaker in Jamaica.
Heh. I'm glad somebody did.
Yeah, I know, I know.
It's rough on jocks.
Get to a certain age,
opportunities dry up.
So here's the deal.
I got this chump, owes me a lot of money,
needs a wake-up call.
What I'd like for you to do isÉ
É use that patented left hook on him.
Just in the ring, Art, you know?
Just in the ring.
Yeah, I'm hip, I'm hipÉ
É but I'll give you two grand.
When you're doneÉ
É all you gotta do is mosey on by the office
and pick up the cash.
Why you wanna come at me
that way, Art?
You know I'm trying to
get back with my wife.
We used to have problems
with that same kind of shit.
I've changed, man.
I found Allah, I don't eat pork,
and I'm a better man.
I faced that demon.
I don't want him coming out again.
You gave up pork.
General, they're sending coordinates.
- Where are they landing?
- Pahrump. It's in the Nevada desert.
Yes, sir. I can have my troops there
at 0800 hours, sir.
Mr. President, we must not send
these people the wrong message.
We need a welcome mat,
not a row of tanks.
What the hell are you talking about?
You can't have Martians
running all over Nevada!
- You're right, general.
- Thank you, sir.
The situation needs to be supervised.
Absolutely, sir.
General CaseyÉ
É you think you can handle it?
I'd be proud.
Good, but keep a lid on it.
Key media, good cross-section of guests.
We don't want it
to turn into a zoo out there.
Yes, sir.
They don't know what the hell
they're talking about.
Liberals, intellectualsÉ
É peacemongers, idiots!
Would you please keep it down?
People live here.
General Casey.
Yes, I get to greet the Martian ambassador.
Isn't that great?
Oh, it's a hell of an honor.
But didn't I always tell you, honeyÉ
É if I just stayed in place
and never spoke upÉ
É good things were bound to happen?
Yeah. Okay.
I want the Martians to be treated
like foreign dignitaries.
I want your men alert and majesticÉ
É with a snap in their step.
This has got to look good.
The whole world is watching.
Yes, sir.
Are you positive
this thing is gonna work?
Positively positive.
We don't want any slip-ups.
No, no, no. Not at all. No.
Hey, Poppy. All these peopleÉ
É all of them here to see you.
Mm-mwah.
There's Jason, Poppy.
Hi, Jason!
Hi.
Jason.
Hi. Yoo-hoo.
All right, let's go.
The teeming masses have gathered
from who knows how many statesÉ
É waiting and watching.
Why have they come?
Curiosity? Or is it something more?
Or is it simply to say, "I was there"?
"I was there when first manÉ
É met Martian."
Jason Stone, GNN, Pahrump.
Give them room.
That's it. Give them room.
It is an awesome sight.
The giant spacecraft glintingÉ
É in the Nevada sun like a giantÉ
É hubcap.
Something's happening.
Doorway is opening.
A silver ramp is coming outÉ
É like a giant tongue. Oh.
Gee whiz.
Rusty. Shh.
Martians.
Funny little critters, ain't they?
Well?
Wait a moment.
Greetings. I am the Martian ambassador.
Everything is fixed now, general.
You may speak.
Greetings. I am General CaseyÉ
É commanding officer of the armed forces
of the United States of America.
On behalf of the people of Earth,
welcome.
He did that well.
We come in peace.
We come in peace. We come in peace.
They came in peace.
We come in peace.
Open fire!
Whoa!
What the hell is this?
Nathalie!
Die, you alien shithead!
Uh-oh.
I surrender.
No, that ain't happening.
That didn't happen.
Nathalie.
Aah!
Holy mother of God.
Did you see that?
We should hit these assholes
with everything we got, sir.
Sir, Mr. President,
I know this seems terribleÉ
É but let's not be too rash.
We should nuke them now, sir.
We must establish
a line of communication first.
Why not set up a town hall?
We can get the public's opinion.
What do you think, Marsha?
Kick the crap out of them.
Ladies and gentlemenÉ
É this could be
a cultural misunderstanding.
Yeah. Maybe to them, doves mean war.
We all saw how they reacted
to that dove.
It frightened them.
He did say thatÉ
É "We come in peace."
Yes.
The new computer's ready,
Mr. President.
Okay, let's do it.
I know we're making the right decision.
Ready to transmit.
This is the president
of the United States.
I'm speaking to you in the hopeÉ
É that what happened earlier today
in the Nevada desertÉ
É was a cultural misunderstanding.
There can be no doubt
that we two peoplesÉ
É have a great deal to offer one another.
You must be as excited as weÉ
É to find intelligent life
in the solar system.
And let me make it clear:
You have nothing to fear from us.
Our customs may be strange to youÉ
É but we mean no harm.
When the investors fly inÉ
É I would like for them each
to be met by a limo.
Top-of-the-line carsÉ
É leather interiorsÉ
É Corinthian, if they got it.
Art, are you still spinning your wheels
on that cockamamie hotel?
- Whoa.
- Hello.
The Martians have attacked.
This was no misunderstanding.
I was there. I saw it.
Look, you're worried about yesterday.
But I'm worried about tomorrow.
The Martians land on Earth,
they're gonna need a place to stay.
Just like everybody else.
My God.
Maybe we should all be destroyed.
The human race doesn't deserve to live.
Ethel, that reminds me.
I would like for every limo to be stockedÉ
É with every kind of alcohol
known to man.
And top it off
with a bottle of Dom on ice.
What confounds me most of all,
gentlemen, is the lack of genitalia.
And of course down here we have the aorta.
Up here we have the sphinx.
Notice the highly developed
cranial nerve system here.
This explains, of course,
the cerebral arteries.
And if we notice down here,
behind the optic chiasmÉ
É several glandsÉ
Very curious.
He who believes in me,
though he die, yet shall he live.
And whoever lives and believes in me
shall never die.
Billy Glenn Norris gave his life
defending our country.
Why did it have to be him?
Billy Glenn Norris is a true American hero.
May God rest his soul.
Ready. Aim.
Fire.
Aim. Fire.
Hello?
Byron. Is everything all right?
You still coming tomorrow?
You just try and stop me.
That plane arrives at 4 p.m.
- Are the kids there?
- Yeah, hold on.
Cedric. Neville.
- Me first.
- No, me.
- Hey, Dad.
- Who's that? Neville?
- Yeah.
- How you doing?
- We're going to the White House.
- You're going to the White House?
Yeah, tomorrow.
- Man, give it back.
- Leave me alone.
It's a school thing, like a tour.
So that means you're still going to school
once in a while?
Yeah.
- Give me your ma again, all right?
- All right. Hold on. Mom.
- You always get to the phone first.
- So what?
Well, I'm first to the game.
What are you wasting this phone time for?
We're gonna see you tomorrow.
Yeah, but there's something
I want to say to you.
Just because I feel like saying it,
all right?
Yeah, what's that?
I love you.
I love you too, Byron.
Now stop wasting money.
I'll see you tomorrow.
They're responding.
A message from the Martians.
- Really?
- They've issued a formal apology.
This is great.
Didn't I tell you this would happen?
The Martian ambassador feels terrible
and asked permission to speak to Congress.
I mean, that's good, isn't it?
You bet.
It's a great victory for our administration.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This is a proud day for all Americans.
This is a hell of a photo op, Jerry.
Are you sure I shouldn't be there?
For some picky reason, the Secret Service
don't want the executive branchÉ
É and the legislative branch
in the same room at the same time.
The Martian ambassador
is gonna say a few words.
Come on down, Mr. Ambassador.
Oh.
Mr. Ambassador, please!
Mr. Ambassador. What are you doing?
This doesn't make sense!
It's not logical! It's notÑ
Guess it wasn't the dove.
Fire!
They blew up Congress.
What did they do that for?
Maybe they don't liking
the human being.
Hello, gentlemen.
Nice of you to come
on such short notice.
General Decker,
it seems I owe you an apology.
Hey, we all make mistakes,
Mr. President.
Not anymore.
We're going to take charge of this thing.
Excellent, sir. I have prepared the order.
What's this?
Oh, that's your executive order authorizing
full use of our nuclear deterrent, sir.
Are you out of your mind?
I'm not going to start a war.
We're already at war, sir.
We have to nuke them.
We have to nuke them now!
General Decker, if you do not shut upÉ
É I'm going to relieve you
of your command.
We have to strike now, sir.
Annihilate. Kill! Kill! Kill!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
NowÉ
É I want the people to knowÉ
É that they still have two out of three
branches of government working for themÉ
É and that ain't bad.
I want the people to know
that the schools will still be open, okay?
And I want the people to knowÉ
É that the garbage
will still be carried out.
And I want a cop on every corner.
Which, incidentallyÉ
É we would already haveÉ
É if they had listened to me
in the last election.
JerryÉ
É how soon can we go on the air?
UhÉ
My fellow AmericansÉ
É it is with a heavy heartÉ
É that I speak to you this afternoon.
As you knowÉ
É earlier today the Martian ambassador
and his confederatesÉ
É attacked and killed many
of your representatives on Capitol Hill.
I will be conferring with other world leaders
as time goes on.
And rest assured that,
working togetherÉ
É we will soon come outÉ
É at a very real outcome.
Thank you.
Hmm.
Oh.
Nathalie?
Nathalie, is that you?
Yes. How are you feeling?
Not terribly good, I'm afraid.
May I ask you a question?
Mm. Yes.
Yes, of course you can, Nathalie.
Were you flirting with me on the show?
Because if you wereÉ
É I just want you to know that I liked it.
Ha-ha. You did? Really?
Because, you know,
I've watched you on TV quite a bitÉ
É and, well, I've had something
of a schoolboy crush on you forÉ
É oh, gosh, ages.
Hi there.
Are you interested in the White House?
I work there. I'm the press secretary.
My name's Jerry Ross.
Maybe you've heard of me?
You wouldn't believe
the pressure of my job.
It's nice to see a new face.
Hey, are you doing anything?
Because if you want,
I could give you a personalized tour.
Would you like that?
Hey, Mitch, it's me. Can you let me in?
Oh, hello, Mr. Ross. Sure.
We're a little nervous here,
after what happened.
Exactly.
Many great men and women
have passed through here.
Now we're passing through here.
Feels good, don't it?
You're very graceful.
I like that.
Come here.
We call this the Kennedy Room.
Pretty nifty, huh?
So how's about a drink?
Ah. Getting more comfortable, I see.
Outstanding.
How's my lady doing?
Oh, missy, you're hot.
But could we get that gum
out of your mouth?
Oh!
My finger!
Hello? Hello, operator?
Operator, this is an emergency!
Help! Please!
Don't shoot.
Don't worry, darling.
Get down!
- Thank you, Mitch.
- It's my job.
Jimmy. Aah! Jimmy.
What's happening?
They appear to be in a highly agitated state,
Nathalie. And I don't know.
I honestly don't know, Nathalie.
I don't know what's going on anymore.
This is frustrating.
I'm just not feeling myself. Nathalie,
if only I could hold you in my arms.
Oh, Donald. I'm scared.
Excuse me.
But you said you wanted to knowÉ
É as soon as we had an analysis
of the gum.
- What is it?
- It's NO2.
Highly concentrated.
Nitrogen.
So that's how it could breathe
in our atmosphere.
What's that noise?
Theodore, I simply do not feel
that LincolnÉ
It's a full-scale invasion. Mr. President,
we're gonna need to get you to safety.
Can we go this way?
Sorry, ma'am.
There's a tour going through here.
The Blue Room is often consideredÉ
É the most beautiful room
in the White House.
In fact, it is often used by the president
to receive guests.
It is furnished to represent the period
of James Monroe.
Hey, what's that?
That is a portrait of James Monroe.
Go, go!
- We lost Taffy.
- Oh, no.
Mr. President, please. Keep moving.
We have to get you to the back stairs!
The Nancy Reagan chandelier.
Marsha!
Marsha?
What are you guys gawking at?
Get that president out of here!
And I personally guaranteeÉ
É that you will get a complete return
on your investmentÉ
É within five months.
Mr. Land, excuse me, please.
Just a second, Sheik Rakmula.
Now, even in a time of so-called
intergalactic emergencyÉ
É the people still wanna roll
them bones.
Mr. Land. I believeÑ
Just five more minutes, Quinn.
What I would like
for you gentlemen to doÉ
É is to view our brand-new,
state-of-the-art show room.
It is out of sight.
Gentlemen.
There is no way that we can lose.
Whoa!
It's not unusual to be loved by anyone
It's not unusual to have fun with anyone
But when I see you hanging about
With anyone
It's not unusual to see me cry
I wanna die
I've been trying to call you all day.
The flight's been canceled.
Byron, there's Martians everywhere.
- Hello?
- Byron! Byron!
- I can't hear you!
- Byron!
I gotta get to Washington.
Byron?
Byron? Byron.
Do you know anyone who can fly a plane?
- Yeah, your husband, Art.
- No, he's dead.
I told him this was gonna happen.
I even loaded a plane with supplies.
I want to go to Tahoe, to the Tahoe caves.
It's remote, the Martians won't find it.
Well, where's the plane?
Private airfield.
Other side of the freeway.
- You think they'll fly to Washington, D.C.?
- Why? I wanna go to Tahoe.
You'll find it happens
All the time
Love would never do
What you want it to
Why can't this crazy love
Be mine
Jesus Christ.
Girls, get out! Get out!
Get out! Get out!
There's a Martian right behind me.
Hey, you're Tom Jones, right?
It ain't unusual
Tom, Tom, can I have an autograph?
Anybody got a pen?
- Hey, that was a hell of a punch.
- You'd better get that gun.
- I'm Tom Jones.
- Byron Williams.
Hey, I saw you fight
in Cardiff, Wales once.
- Yeah? Hey, Barbara.
- Yeah?
You all right?
- I need a drink.
- You and me both, baby.
- We better get out.
- You know how to fly a plane?
- Sure. You got one?
- She has.
Don't run, we are your friends.
- Martians blew up the shop.
- You're kidding me?
- Should I get Grandma?
- Forget Grandma.
She's halfway to outer space already.
Here, lock and load.
I'll tell you one thing.
They ain't getting the TV.
The president of France on line two.
Mr. President, the president of France
is on line two.
He says it's important.
Hello, Maurice.
I have some good news for you.
The Martian ambassador is here.
And we've negotiated a settlement.
Maurice, get out of the room.
Get out now.
Mr. President.
I need you to sign this.
What is it?
My last will and testament?
It is an order to deploy
our nuclear capability, sir.
Three, two, one, fire.
What the hell was that?
Look!
What was that?
- Where you going?
- To go get Grandma.
No, you ain't.
Stay and defend this trailer.
That's what Billy Glenn would've done.
- You leave, you're disgracing a hero.
- I don't care. I'm gonna go get Grandma.
- Boy!
- Richie, come back here!
What in the hell is that?
Hey! Cut it out!
Stop it!
- This way.
- No, this way.
Bullshit! The airfield's over there!
Hey. Hey, just because
you're dressed like King TutÉ
É doesn't mean you're our leader.
Look at this. This is wrong!
We're lost. He led us down a maze.
I'm going back to the hotel.
- Come on, this way!
- Wait!
- No, wait! Where are you going?
- Come on, Barbara.
I like him. I do.
Assholes. Why did I listen to them?
I should have stayed in the hotel.
Shit!
I surrender, okay?
You understand what that means?
Surrender?
Lookit. You're intelligent beings.
Let's cut a deal. I can help you.
I'm a lawyer.
You want to conquer the world,
you're gonna need lawyers, right?
Here.
You want my watch?
Take it. Take it. Go on. It's a Rolex.
Rolex.
- Nice shot.
- Yeah, pity I was too late.
Barbara, can I have the gun back, please?
Barbara, give me the gun and come on!
Grandma!
Oh, my God.
When I'm calling you
Richie, I think these guys are very sick.
What's happening to them?
What's killing them?
I think it must be my music.
Ho! Shh! Shh.
Quiet.
You think you can do anything you want.
Well, you can't.
You see, because we are human beings.
And we have the United States ArmyÉ
É that'll fight you to the last man.
And we'll never surrender.
Do you hear me?
We'll fight you on the beaches.
We'll fight you on the street.
We will never, never surrender.
Old Glory will win!
Democracy will survive!
We will never, ever surrender!
We will win!
The eagle will be triumphant!
No.
Why are you doing this?
Why?
Isn't the universe big enoughÉ
É for both of us?
What is wrong with you people?
We could work together.
Why be enemies?
Because we're different?
Is that why?
Think of the things that we could do.
Think how strong we would be.
EarthÉ
É and MarsÉ
É together.
There is nothing
that we could not accomplish.
Think about it.
Why destroyÉ
É when you can create?
We can have it allÉ
É or we can smash it all.
Why can't we work out our differences?
Why can't we work things out?
Little peopleÉ
É why can't we all just get along?
What's this?
Don't run. We are your friends.
Next stop, radio station.
There it is.
Let's move it!
Here it is.
Go get it started.
Barbara, go with him.
- Okay.
- Cindy, come with me.
Tom. Are you sure you can fly this?
Yeah, I think so, yeah.
Who put that on?
- It's stuck.
- Cindy, over here.
Shit.
They haven't seen us yet. Come here.
- Cindy. Get in the plane.
- What?
I'm staying. I'll distract them.
The first chance you get, you take off.
- I'm not leaving you.
- Just do it.
I'll draw them away. Now, go.
- No.
- I said, go!
Oh, my God.
- What's he doing?
- He must have flipped!
- He's going to throw them off.
- Yeah, but we can't leave him.
No weapon. No clown outfit.
Just me!
Byron WilliamsÉ
É heavyweight championÉ
É of the world.
Something's happened.
Something's happened to Byron.
When I'm calling you
Will you answer too
That means I offer my love
Our love will come true
You belong to me
I belong to you
Goodbye, my darling.
I wish things could've been different.
So do I.
Goodbye.
- I love you.
- I love you too, Nathalie.
Florence NorrisÉ
É I hereby present to you
the Congressional Medal of HonorÉ
É the highest decoration
our nation can bestow.
Thank you, honey.
But don't you dare let this happen again.
Richard NorrisÉ
É on behalf of my parents,
who couldn't be here todayÉ
É for saving the world
from the MartiansÉ
É I proudly present to you
the Medal of Honor.
You don't have to kiss me
if you don't want to.
I have to.
I prepared a speech. Is that all right?
Sure, that's very appropriate.
Hi, everybody.
First, I just want to sayÑ
Can you speak up? We can't hear you.
Well, I want to say that there's
a lot of people in the worldÉ
É that have, like,
done a lot more than I haveÉ
É and they're the ones
that should be here now getting a medal.
And I want to thank my grandma
for always being so good to meÉ
É and for helping save the world
and everything.
So I guess, like, now we just have toÉ
É start over and start rebuilding everything,
like our houses.
But I was thinking, maybe instead
of houses, we could live in tepeesÉ
É because it's better in a lot of ways.
Okay, that's all I have to say. Thanks.
- Was that okay?
- Yeah.
Do you got a girlfriend?
No.
Guys, come on. Give me a break.
Go on in there and start cleaning your room.
I can't do all this by myself.
Please? Look at you.
Yeah.